<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ActuA11y</string>

    <!-- Home Screen -->
    <string name="home_screen_title">ActuA11y</string>
    <string name="home_pane_title">Home — ActuA11y</string>
    <string name="home_intro_title">Welcome to ActuA11y</string>
    <string name="home_intro_text">ActuA11y shows how to build accessible Android apps. Browse the topics below to explore different accessibility patterns. If you use TalkBack, switch access, or a keyboard, this app is designed to work well with all of them.</string>
    <string name="home_talkback_category">TalkBack</string>
    <string name="content_descriptions_label">Content Descriptions</string>
    <string name="content_descriptions_list_item_desc">Content Descriptions topic. Learn how images and icon buttons describe themselves to TalkBack. Activates the Content Descriptions topic screen.</string>

    <!-- Content Descriptions Screen -->
    <string name="content_descriptions_title">Content Descriptions</string>
    <string name="content_descriptions_pane_title">Content Descriptions</string>
    <string name="navigate_back">Navigate back</string>
    <string name="content_descriptions_intro">Images and icon buttons need descriptions so TalkBack can read them aloud. Swipe through this screen with TalkBack on to hear how each example works.</string>

    <string name="meaningful_image_section_label">Image with content description</string>
    <string name="meaningful_image_desc">A smartphone icon representing a mobile device</string>
    <string name="meaningful_image_instruction">Focus this image with TalkBack. TalkBack reads aloud the content description set in code.</string>

    <string name="icon_button_section_label">Icon button with content description</string>
    <string name="icon_button_desc">Show information about content descriptions</string>
    <string name="icon_button_instruction">This button has no visible label. TalkBack reads the content description from code so you know what the button does.</string>

    <string name="decorative_image_section_label">Decorative image — skipped by TalkBack</string>
    <string name="decorative_image_instruction">TalkBack skips this image entirely. In code, its content description is set to null, which removes it from the accessibility tree.</string>

    <string name="developer_note_label">Developer note</string>
    <string name="developer_note_body">For meaningful images, pass a non-null string to the Image contentDescription parameter — TalkBack reads it when the image is focused. For decorative images, pass null; Compose removes the node from the accessibility tree entirely.\n\nFor icon-only buttons, set contentDescription on the Icon inside IconButton. This is the only name TalkBack has for that button.\n\nModifier.semantics with paneTitle announces the screen name when a pane appears. Without it, TalkBack gives no feedback when the user navigates to a new screen.\n\nModifier.semantics with heading() marks text as a section heading so TalkBack users can jump between sections using a swipe gesture.\n\nSee: androidx.compose.ui.semantics.SemanticsProperties</string>

    <string name="bad_version_button">Bad version</string>
    <string name="bad_version_toast">Bad version not yet implemented</string>
</resources>
